Guide to the Witchcraft and possession-related movie posters, lobby cards, and other cinema memorabilia, 1916-2015.
Witchcraft and possession-related movie posters, lobby cards, and other cinema memorabilia,
- 1970-1979
  - A-G
    - Dívka na koštěti, 1972 (Mapcase-folder 15)
      The Girl on a Broomstick
      Czechoslovakia
    - La Ragazza sulla Scopa, 1972 (Mapcase-folder 15)
      Poster dated 1982
      Original Czech title: Dívka na Koštěti
    - Lucifer's Women, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Doctor Dracula, 1978 (Mapcase-folder 15)
      Lucifer's Women
    - Donne e Magia con Satanasso in Compagnia, 1973; 2 panels (Mapcase-folder 29)
    - Donne e Magia con Satanasso in Compagnia, 1973 (Mapcase-folder 24)
    - Double Possession, 1973 (Mapcase-folder 15)
      Re-cut version of Ganja and Hess
    - Los Endemoniados, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      Original US Title: The Dunwich Horror
      Hell
      Devil's child
    - The Dunwich Horror, 1970; 3 sheets (Mapcase-folder 29)
      Based on H.P. Lovecraft
      Dunwich Horror
      Lovecraft, H.P.
    - Die Elixiere des Teufels, 1973 (Mapcase-folder 13)
      The Devil's Elixirs
    - Endemoniada, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      The Possessed, aka Demon Witch Child
    - La Endemoniada, 1975 (Mapcase-folder 15)
    - L'Eretica, 1975; 2 panel (Mapcase-folder 30)
      Original Spanish title: La Endemoniada
    - Escalofrio, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Satan's Blood, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      Original Spanish Title: Escalofrio
    - Escalofro Diablico, 1972 (Mapcase-folder 15)
    - L'esorciccio, 1975 (Mapcase-folder 30)
    - El Espanto Surge de la Tumba, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 8)
      Horror Rises from the Tomb
    - Blutmesse fr den Teufel, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      Original Spanish title: El Espanto Surge de la Tumba
    - El Espanto Surge de la Tumba, 1973 (Mapcase-folder 15)
    - Estratto dagli Archivi Segreti della Polizia di una Capitale Europea, 1972; 4 panels (Mapcase-folder 30)
      Tragic Ceremony
    - Trgica Ceremonia, 1972 (Mapcase-folder 15)
      Original Italian title: Estratto dagli Archivi Segreti della Polizia di una Capitale Europea
    - Exorcism, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      Original Spanish title: Exorcismo
    - Exorcismo, 1975 (Mapcase-folder 15)
    - Le Notti de Satana, 1975 (Mapcase-folder 15)
    - Le Notti de Satana, 1975 (Mapcase-folder 15)
    - Le Notti de Satana, 1975; 11 items (Mapcase-folder 15)
    - Le Notti de Satana, 1975; 2 panels (Mapcase-folder 30)
    - The Exorcist, 1973; 8 items (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Der Exorzist—Director’s Cut, 1973; 4 items (Box 5, Folder 12)
      Original U.S. title: The Exorcist
    - L’Esorcista, 1973 (Mapcase-folder 15)
      2010 release of director's cut
    - Exorcist II: The Heretic, 1977 (Mapcase-folder 15)
    - Exorcisme et Messes Noires, 1979 (Mapcase-folder 30)
      Demoniac, and Black Masses (X-Rated Version), Exorcisms (video title)
      Original French title: L'ventreur de Notre-Dame
    - L'ventreur de Notre-Dame, 1975; 2 panels (Mapcase-folder 30)
    - Leva lo Diavolo Tuo dal... Convento, 1973 (Mapcase-folder 24)
      The Countess Died of Laughter; Devils in the Convent
      Original German title: Frau Wirtins tolle Tchterlein
  - H-O
    - The Naked Wytche, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 5)
      The Naked Wytche
      Original German title: Hnsel und Gretel Verliefen Sich im Wald
    - Hnsel und Gretel Verliefen Sich im Wald, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Hnsel und Gretel Verliefen Sich im Wald, 1970 (Mapcase-folder 16)
    - Haunted, 1977 (Mapcase-folder 16)
    - Help me...I'm Possessed, 1974 (Mapcase-folder 16)
    - Mark of the Devil, 1970; 7 items (Box 5, Folder 6)
      Original German title: Hexen bis aufs Blut Geqult
      Australia
      Witch hunting
      Witch trials
      Torture
    - Hexen Geschndet und zu Tode Geqult, 1973 (Mapcase-folder 16)
    - Mark of the Devil, 1970 (Mapcase-folder 17)
    - Mark of the Devil, 1970 (Mapcase-folder 25)
    - Les Sorcires Sanglantes, 1970 (Box exhibit)
      Mark of the Devil
      Flemish title: Bloedige Heksenjacht;Original German title: Hexen bis aufs Blut Geqult
    - La Tortura delle Vergini, 1970 (Box exhibit)
    - Le Streghe Nere, 1973 (Box exhibit)
      Original German title: Hexen Geschndet und zu Tode Geqult
    - Hexen bis aufs Blut geqult, 1974 (Box exhibit)
      U.K./West German co-production
      U.K. title: Mark of the Devil Part 2
    - Mark of the Devil Part II, 1973 (Mapcase-folder 17)
    - La Maison du Peche Mortel, 1976 (Mapcase-folder 24)
    - La Mansin Embrujada, 1973 (Mapcase-folder 16)
      Original U.K. title: The House That Dripped Blood;House in Nightmare Park
    - La Casa che Grondava Sangue, 1973 (Mapcase-folder 24)
    - The House That Dripped Blood, 1971 (Mapcase-folder 16)
      Case involvling a little girl who displays an interest in witchcraft
      Lee, Christopher, 1922-2015
      Cushing, Peter, 1913-1994
      Israel
    - Season of the Witch, 1972 (Mapcase-folder 20)
      Romero, George
    - Sharon's Baby, 1975 (Mapcase-folder 24)
      Original US title: I Don't Want To Be Born
    - Sharon's Baby, 1975; 4 panels (Mapcase-folder 30)
    - Sharon's Baby, 1975; 2 panels (Mapcase-folder 30)
    - Il Cocktail del Diavolo, 1971; 2 panels (Mapcase-folder 30)
      Original U.S. title: If He Hollers, Let Him Go!
    - Inquisicin, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 8)
      Inquisition
      Witchfinder
      Pact with the devil
    - Inquisicin, 1976 (Box exhibit)
    - El Inquisidor Las Brujas Desnudas, 1975; 4 items (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Die Wiege des Satans, 1974 (Mapcase-folder 16)
      Original U.S. title: It's Alive
    - Black Magic, 1975 (Mapcase-folder 24)
      Original Chinese title: Jiang tou
      China
    - Black Magic, 1975 (Mapcase-folder 16)
    - Martillo Para las Brujas, 1970; 5 items (Box 4, Folder 5)
      Witchhammer, aka Witches’ Hammer
      Original Czech title: Kladivo na čarodějnice
    - Kladivo na čarodějnice, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - El Ltigo Contra Satans, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 5)
      Western
    - Legend of the Witches, 1970; 2 items (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Lemora: A Child's Tale of the Supernatural, 1973 (Mapcase-folder 24)
    - Lemora La Metamorfosi di Satana, 1973; 2 panels (Mapcase-folder 30)
      Lomora: A Child's Tale of the Supernatural
    - Leonor, 1975 (Mapcase-folder 17)
    - Confessioni Proibite di una Monaca Adolescente, 1977; 2 items (Mapcase-folder 24)
    - La Casa del Exorcismo, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      The House of Exorcism is a re-cut 1975 re-release of Lisa and the Devil (1973)
      Original Italian title: Lisa e il diavolo aka La casa dell'esorcismo
    - The House of Exorcism, 1975 (Mapcase-folder 16)
      The House of Exorcism
    - El Diablo se Lleva Los Muertos, 1975 (Mapcase-folder 17)
    - La Casa dell’Esorcismo, 1975 (Mapcase-folder 23)
    - La Casa dell’esorcismo, 1975 (Mapcase-folder 30)
    - Magdalena, vom Teufel besessen, 1974; 3 items (Mapcase-folder 17)
    - Magdalena, vom Teufel besessen, 1974; 2 items (Mapcase-folder 17)
      Beyond the Darkness
    - Il Maligno, 1975; 4 Panels (Mapcase-folder 31)
    - Malocchio, 1975; 4 panels (Mapcase-folder 31)
      Evil Eye
    - Malocchio, 1975; 2 panels (Mapcase-folder 31)
      - El Mariscal del Infierno, 1974 (Mapcase-folder 17)
        Devil's Possessed
      - Marika Degli Inferni, 1974 (Mapcase-folder 25)
        Mariken - A Medieval Allegory
        Original Dutch title: Mariken van Nieumeghen
      - The Devil's Possessed, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 5)
        Original Italian title: El Mariscal del Infierno
      - El Regreso de la Bruja, 1970; 2 items (Box 4, Folder 5)
        Mark of the Witch
      - Mark of the Witch, 1970 (Mapcase-folder 17)
      - Emilie l'Enfant des Tnbres, 1975 (Mapcase-folder 17)
        The Night Child
        Original Italian title: Il Medaglione Insanguinato
      - Il Medaglione Insanguinato, 1975; 2 panels (Mapcase-folder 31)
      - Il Medaglione Insanguinato, 1975; 4 panels (Mapcase-folder 31)
      - Emilie l'Enfant des Tnbres, 1975 (Mapcase-folder 31)
      - Exorcism’s Daughter, 1971 (Mapcase-folder 15)
        Original Spanish title: Las Melanclicas
      - Mephisto Waltz, 1971; 8 items (Box 5, Folder 8)
        Soul-switching
      - Mephisto Waltz, 1971 (Mapcase-folder 17)
      - Satan Mon Amour, 1971 (Mapcase-folder 25)
        Original U.S. title: Mephisto Waltz
      - La Macchia della Morte, 1971; 2 panels (Mapcase-folder 31)
      - La Macchia della Morte, 1971; 4 panels (Mapcase-folder 31)
      - I Satans Vold, 1972 (Mapcase-folder 17)
        The Monk
        Original French title: Le Moine
        Monks
        Papacy
      - Der Mnch und die Frauen, 1972 (Mapcase-folder 17)
      - Sisters of Satan, 1973 (Mapcase-folder 17)
        Original Italian title: Le Monache di Sant’Arcangelo
      - Le Monache di Sant’Arcangelo, 1973; 2 panels (Mapcase-folder 31)
        Innocents from Hell; Sisters of Satan; The Nun and the Devil; The Nuns of Saint Archangel
      - Le Diavolesse, 1973 (Mapcase-folder 25)
        Girl Slaves of Morgana Le Fay
        Original French title: Morgane et Ses Nymphes (1971)
      - Le Diavolesse, 1973; 5 items (Mapcase-folder 25)
      - Il Nano e la Strega, 1973; 4 panels (Mapcase-folder 32)
        King Dick
      - Il Nano e la Strega, 1973; 4 panels (Mapcase-folder 32)
      - Night of Dark Shadows, 1971 (Mapcase-folder 18)
      - Night of Dark Shadows, 1971 (Mapcase-folder 25)
      - La Casa delle Ombre Maledette, 1971 (Mapcase-folder 25)
        Original title: Night of Dark Shadows
      - La Casa delle Ombre Maledette, 1971; 2 panels (Mapcase-folder 32)
      - La Noche de los Brujos, 1971; 3 items (Box 2, Folder 9)
        U.S./Canadian co-production
        Night of the Witches
      - La Noche de los Brujos, 1974 (Mapcase-folder 18)
        de Ossorio, Amando
      - La Longue Nuit de l’Exorcisme, 1972 (Mapcase-folder 25)
        Don't Torture a Duckling
        Original Italian title: Non Si Sevizia un Paperino
      - La Noche de los Diablos, 1972 (Mapcase-folder 18)
        Night of the Devils
        Original Italian title: La Notte dei Diavoli
      - La Nuit Des Diables, 1972 (Mapcase-folder 25)
      - Nuda per Satana, 1974; 2 panels (Mapcase-folder 32)
        Nude for Satan
      - Un’Ombra Nell’Ombra, 1979 (Mapcase-folder 18)
        Ring of Darkness
      - Un’Ombra Nell’Ombra, 1979 (Mapcase-folder 25)
      - The Obsessed One, 1974 (Mapcase-folder 18)
        Original US title: Operation Makonaima
      - Hanging Woman, 1973 (Mapcase-folder 18)
        Terror of the Living Dead
        Original Spanish title: La Orga de los Muertos
      - La Orga de los Muertos, 1973; 2 items (Mapcase-folder 18)
        Hanging Woman; Terror of the Living Dead
      - Poseida, 1978; 2 items (Mapcase-folder 18)
        Obscene Desire
        Original Italian title: l’Osceno Desiderio
      - L’Osceno Desiderio, 1978; 4 panels (Mapcase-folder 32)
      - L’Osceno Desiderio, 1978; 4 panels (Mapcase-folder 32)
      - Enter the Devil, 1972; 14 items (Box 5, Folder 11)
        1 8x10 negative - U.S. presskit
        Re-release of Enter the Devil
      - Disciples of Death, 1972 (Mapcase-folder 14)
      - Sexorcists, 1974 (Mapcase-folder 21)
      - L’Ossessa, 1974; 4 panels (Mapcase-folder 32)
        Enter the Devil, The Devil Obsession, The Sexorcist, The Tormented
      - Exorcisation, 1974 (Mapcase-folder 32)
        Original Italian title: L’Ossessa
      - L'Ossessa - Das Omen des Bsen, 1974 (Mapcase-folder 18)
  - P-Z
    - Quella Strega di Pippi Calzelunghe, 1970 (Mapcase-folder 25)
      Pippi on the Run
      Original Swedish title: P rymmen med Pippi Lngstrump
    - La Perversa Caricia de Satan, 1976 (Mapcase-folder 19)
      Devil's Kiss
    - The Devil's Wedding Night, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      Tagline: “EXORCISM! The one last hope for the possessed... BUT THIS TIME THE DEVIL WINS!”
      Original Italian title: Il Plenilunio delle Vergini
    - Il Plenilunio delle Vergini, 1973; 5 items (Mapcase-folder 25)
      The Devil's Wedding Night
    - Les Vierges de la Pleine Lune, 1973 (Mapcase-folder 25)
      Original Italian title: Il Plenilunio delle Vergini; Flemish title: De Maagden van de Volle Maan
    - Devil's Nightmare, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 5)
      Belgian/Italian co-production
      Original Belgian title:La Plus Longue Nuit du Diable
    - Au Service du Diable, 1971; 2 items (Mapcase-folder 19)
      The Devil’s Nightmare
    - Vampire Playgirls, 1971 (Mapcase-folder 19)
      The Devil's Nightmare; Vampire Playgirls
    - La Terrificante Notte del Demonio, 1971 (Mapcase-folder 25)
    - Au Service du Diable, 1971 (Mapcase-folder 25)
    - Au Service du Diable, 1971 (Mapcase-folder 25)
    - Au Service du Diable, 1971 (Mapcase-folder 33)
    - La Plus Longue Nuit du Diable, 1971; 2 panels (Mapcase-folder 33)
    - Sexy Diabolic Story, 1974 (Mapcase-folder 26)
      Lorna the Exorcist; Linda
      Original French title: Les Possdes du Diable
    - Possession of Joel Delaney, 1970; 7 items (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - The Possession of Joel Delaney, 1972; 2 items (Mapcase-folder 19)
    - Possession, 1970 (Mapcase-folder 25)
      Possession of Joel Delaney
    - Necromancy, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 6)
      The Witching
    - Necromancy, 1972 (Mapcase-folder 18)
    - Il Potere di Satana, 1972 (Mapcase-folder 25)
      Necromancy; The Witching
    - Il Potere di satana, 1972; 2 panels (Mapcase-folder 32)
    - Profezia, 1979; 2 panels (Mapcase-folder 33)
      Original U.S. title: Prophecy
    - The Pyx, 1973 (Mapcase-folder 19)
      Canadian production
    - Una Squillo Scomoda per l’Ispettore Newman, 1973; 2 panels (Mapcase-folder 33)
      Original Canadian title: The Pyx;The Hooker Cult Murders;La Lunule (French Canadian title)
    - Una squillo scomoda per l'ispettore Newman, 1973; 2 panels (Mapcase-folder 33)
    - Una squillo scomoda per l'ispettore Newman, 1973; 2 panels (Mapcase-folder 33)
    - Una squillo scomoda per l'ispettore Newman, 1973; 2 panels (Mapcase-folder 33)
    - Quant' bella la Bernarda, tutta nera, tutta calda, 1975 (Mapcase-folder 26)
    - Il Sessorcista, 1975 (Mapcase-folder 26)
      Original Italian title: Quant' bella la Bernarda, tutta nera, tutta calda
    - Il Sessorcista, 1975; 2 panels (Mapcase-folder 33)
    - The Hex Massacre, 1978 (Mapcase-folder 16)
      Original Spanish title: Quin puede matar a un nio?
    - Race With the Devil, 1975; 2 items (Mapcase-folder 19)
    - In Corsa con il Diavolo, 1975 (Mapcase-folder 26)
      Original U.S. title: Race with the Devil
    - Course Contre l’Enfer, 1975 (Mapcase-folder 33)
    - Die Beschwrung des Teufels, 1973 (Mapcase-folder 19)
      Vengeance of the Zombies
      Original Spanish title: La Rebelin de las Muertas
    - Les Sorcires du Lac, 1970 (Mapcase-folder 26)
      Queens of Evil
      Original Italian title: Le Regine
    - Svirepo Nežne, 1970 (Mapcase-folder 26)
      Italian/French co-production
      Original Italian title: Le Regine;Il Delitto del Diavolo; French title: Les Sorcires au Bord du Lac
    - Le Regine, 1970; 4 panels (Mapcase-folder 33)
      Alternate Italian title: Il Delitto del Diavolo;French title: Les Sorcires au Bord du Lac
    - Return from Witch Mountain, 1978 (Mapcase-folder 19)
    - La papesse, 1975; 2 panels (Mapcase-folder 33)
      Italian title: I riti erotici della papessa Jesial
    - Riti, Magie Nere e Segrete Orge nel Trecento, 1973 (Mapcase-folder 26)
      Black Magic Rites: Reincarnations; The Reincarnation of Isabel
    - Ruby, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 5)
      Spanish title: Ruby, Posesion Satanica
    - Ruby, 1977 (Mapcase-folder 26)
    - Ruby, 1977; 2 panels (Mapcase-folder 33)
    - Santo contra la magia negra, 1973 (Mapcase-folder 20)
    - Der Satan, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      Sweet Savior
    - Satanico Pandemonium, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - La Novizia Indemoniata, 1975 (Mapcase-folder 26)
      Original Spanish title: Satanico Pandemonium
    - Satanico Pandemonium, 1975 (Mapcase-folder 26)
    - Satan's Cheerleaders, 1977 (Mapcase-folder 20)
    - Satans de Todos los Horrores, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 5)
      Poe, Edgar Allan, 1809-1849
    - La Satanica, 1973 (Mapcase-folder 20)
    - Satan's Children, 1975 (Mapcase-folder 20)
    - Satan's Slave, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 9)
      Satan's Slave, aka Evil Heritage
      Coven
    - L'Esclave de Satan, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Satan's Slave, 1976 (Mapcase-folder 20)
    - Sklavin des Satans, 1976 (Mapcase-folder 20)
    - Schiave di Satana, 1977 (Mapcase-folder 20)
      France/West German co-production
    - Le Scomunicate di San Valentino, 1974 (Mapcase-folder 20)
      The Sinful Nuns of Saint Valentine
    - Secret Rites, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Riti Segreti, 1970; 2 panels (Mapcase-folder 34)
      Original U.K. title: Secret Rites
    - Riti Segreti, 1970; 4 panels (Mapcase-folder 34)
    - El Segundo Poder, 1976; 4 items (Box 2, Folder 9)
      The Second Power
    - Les Nuits Sexuelles, 1971 (Mapcase-folder 25)
      Night of the Damned; Night of the Sexual Demons
      Flemish title: Seksuele Nachten;Original Italian title: La Notte dei Dannati
    - La Notte dei Dannati, 1971; 2 panels (Mapcase-folder 32)
    - The Sentinel, 1977; 2 items (Mapcase-folder 20)
      Hexen Sabbat
    - Sensitivit, 1979; 4 panels (Mapcase-folder 34)
      The House by the Edge of the Lake
    - Il Sesso della Strega, 1973; 3 items (Mapcase-folder 26)
      Sex of the Witch
    - Simon—King of the Witches, 1971; 2 items; Taglines: “The Black Mass... The Spells... The Incantations... The Curses... The Ceremonial Sex...” (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Simon—Rey de los Brujos, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 9)
      Simon—King of the Witches
    - Simon—King of the Witches, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Simon—King of the Witches, 1971 (Mapcase-folder 26)
    - Robin Hood und die Dmonen des Satans, 1970 (Mapcase-folder 21)
      Original Italian title: Una Spada per Brando
    - Una Spada per Brando, 1970 (Mapcase-folder 26)
    - Mač za Brandoa, 1970 (Mapcase-folder 26)
    - Vierges Pour Satana, 1970 (Mapcase-folder 34)
    - Una Spada per Brando, 1970; 2 panels (Mapcase-folder 34)
    - Las Dos Caras de Julia, 1978; 12 items (Box 2, Folder 8)
      Summer of Fear, aka Stranger in Our House
    - Cadı, 1978 (Mapcase-folder 12)
      Summer of Fear, aka Stanger in Our House
      Turkey
    - Summer of Fear, 1978 (Mapcase-folder 21)
      Stranger in Our House
    - Leto Užasa, 1978 (Mapcase-folder 26)
    - Sugar Hill, 1974 (Mapcase-folder 21)
    - Suspiria, 1977; 2 items (Mapcase-folder 26)
    - Terror, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Terror, 1978; 2 items (Mapcase-folder 21)
    - La Monja Poseda, 1976; Postcard size. (Box 5, Folder 5)
      Original U.K. title: To the Devil a Daughter.
    - To The Devil a Daughter, 1976; 5 items (Mapcase-folder 21)
      British/West German co-production
      Britain
    - Touch of Melissa, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 9)
      The Touch of Satan
    - The Touch of Satan, 1971; 2 items (Box 4, Folder 5)
      Press kits
    - El Toque de Satanas, 1971; 4 items (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - The Touch of Satan, 1971; 18 items (Box 5, Folder 9)
      Inlcudes a recepit for photos and original title header that appears on the photos.
    - The Touch of Satan, 1971 (Mapcase-folder 21)
    - L’Amante di Satana, 1971 (Mapcase-folder 27)
    - Touch of Melissa, 1971 (Mapcase-folder 27)
    - L'ossessa - I raccapriccianti delitti di Monroe Park, 1971; 4 panels (Mapcase-folder 32)
      Original U.S. title: The Touch of Satan
    - Il sesso della strega, 1973; 4 panels (Mapcase-folder 34)
    - Il Sesso del Diavolo, 1971; 2 panels (Mapcase-folder 35)
      Original Italian title: Trittico
    - Der Hexentter von Blackmoor, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 8)
      Liechtenstein/Italy/Spain/West Germany co-production
      Night of the Blood Monster; The Bloody Judge
      Original Italian title: Il Trono de Fuoco
    - Night of the Blood Monster, 1970; 8 items (Box 2, Folder 9)
      The Bloody Judge
      Lee, Christopher, 1922-2016
    - Il Trono de Fuoco, 1970 (Mapcase-folder 21)
      Lee, Christopher, 1922-2017
    - El Proceso de las Brujas, 1970 (Mapcase-folder 22)
      The Bloody Judge, Night of the Blood Monster
      Lee, Christopher, 1922-2018
    - Il Trono de Fuoco, 1970 (Mapcase-folder 27)
      Lee, Christopher, 1922-2019
    - Tutti I Colori del Buio, 1972 (Mapcase-folder 27)
      They're Coming to Get You; All the Colors of the Dark
    - They’re Coming to Get You, 1972 (Mapcase-folder 22)
      Alternate U.S. title: All the Colors of the Dark
      Original Italian title: Tutti I Colori del Buio
    - Todos Los Colores de la Oscuridad, 1972 (Mapcase-folder 22)
    - Sve Boje Mraka, 1972 (Mapcase-folder 27)
    - Hijas de Dracula, 1971; 4 items (Box 2, Folder 7)
      Original U.K. title: Twins of Evil
    - Daughters of Satan, 1972; 8 items (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Twins of Evil, 1971 (Mapcase-folder 22)
    - Le Figlie di Dracula, 1971; 2 panels (Mapcase-folder 35)
    - Le Figlie di Dracula, 1971; 4 panels (Mapcase-folder 35)
    - El Regreso de el Exorcista, 1975 (Mapcase-folder 22)
      Original Italian title: Un Urlo Dalle Tenebre
    - Un Urlo dalle Tenebre, 1975 (Mapcase-folder 27)
      The Return of the Exorcist
    - Un Urlo dalle Tenebre, 1975; 4 panels (Mapcase-folder 35)
    - Esorcismo Nero, 1973 (Mapcase-folder 27)
      Original French title: Vaudou
    - Virgin Witch, 1972; 2 items (Mapcase-folder 22)
      Style B
    - La Sorciere Vierge, 1972 (Mapcase-folder 27)
      Original U.K. title: Virgin Witch
    - Messe Nere per Le Vergini Svedesi, 1972 (Mapcase-folder 27)
    - Brujas Salvajes, 1972; 9 items (Mapcase-folder 27)
    - Messe Nere per le Vergini Svedisi, 1972; 2 sheets (Mapcase-folder 35)
    - Vud Sangriento, 1974 (Mapcase-folder 22)
      Voodoo Black Exorcist
    - Warlock Moon, 1973 (Mapcase-folder 22)
- 1980-1989
  - 976-EVIL, 1988 (Mapcase-folder 38)
  - Aenigma, 1987; 2 panels (Mapcase-folder 43)
  - L'altro Inferno, 1981; 6 items (Mapcase-folder 36)
    The Other Hell
  - Guardian of Hell, 1981 (Mapcase-folder 38)
    Original Italian title: L'altro Inferno
  - Terror en el Convento, 1981 (Mapcase-folder 38)
  - L'altro inferno, 1981; 2 panels (Mapcase-folder 43)
  - L'altro inferno, 1981; 2 panels (Mapcase-folder 43)
  - American Risci, 1989; 2 panels (Mapcase-folder 43)
    American Rickshaw
  - Amityville II - Le possede, 1982 (Mapcase-folder 36)
    Original U.S. title: Amityville II: The Possessed
  - Bay Coven, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Fanatici Zla, 1987 (Mapcase-folder 36)
    Original U.S. title: The Believers
    Schlesinger, John, 1926-2003
    Croatia
  - Tarikat, 1987 (Mapcase-folder 38)
    Isreal
  - The Believers, 1987 (Mapcase-folder 38)
  - The Believers, 1987; 2 panels (Mapcase-folder 43)
  - Beyond Evil, 1980 (Mapcase-folder 38)
  - La Bimba di Satana, 1982 (Mapcase-folder 38)
    Satan's Baby Doll, aka A Girl for Satan
  - La Bimba di Satana, 1982; 2 panels (Mapcase-folder 43)
  - Los Ritos Sexuales del Diablo, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    Original U.S. Title: Black Candles
  - Brujas Magicas, 1981; 12 items (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - La Casa 3, 1988 (Mapcase-folder 36)
  - La Casa 3, 1989; 2 panels (Mapcase-folder 43)
  - Witchraft—Das Böse Lebt, 1988 (Mapcase-folder 38)
    Witchery
    Original Spanish title: La Casa 4 (Witchcraft)
  - La Casa 4 (Witchcraft), 1988; 2 panels (Mapcase-folder 43)
  - La Chiesa, 1989; 2 panels (Mapcase-folder 43)
    The Church
  - Clash of the Titans, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Deadly Blessing, 1981; 8 items (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Dmoni 2... l'incubo ritorna, 1986; 2 panels (Mapcase-folder 44)
    Demons 2
  - Les Doigts du Diable, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    Original U.S. title: Demonoid
  - Macabra: La Garra Del Diablo, 1980 (Mapcase-folder 39)
  - Les Doigts du Diable, 1981 (Mapcase-folder 44)